wellingtonnz.com 2007-10-11

# Positively Wellington Tourism Privacy Undertaking

|  Privacy Statement of Positively Wellington Tourism  
  
---  
  
## Information about our Organisation and Web site

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organisation like Positively Wellington Tourism . We are based in New Zealand .   
Our principal activity is: Tourism Marketing   
Our privacy policy covers Positively Wellington Tourism and its Web site: 

**Organisation Name:** Positively Wellington Tourism **  
Address:** Level 28, Grand Plimmer Tower, Gilmer Terrace   
**City, Post Code:** Wellington 6011, P O Box 10 017  
 **Country:** New Zealand   
**Controller:** Positively Wellington Tourism   
**Web Site:** [www.WellingtonNZ.com](http://www.wellingtonnz.com/)

## Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access

  * You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data. 

## The services and links of our Web site 

  * Our Web site does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. 
  * Our Web site includes links to third party Web service providers. 

## Automatic Collection of Information 

  * We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. 
  * We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. 

## Data Collection and Purpose Specification 

  * We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. 
  * We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations. 
  * To access the table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used, please [click here](http://wellingtonnz.com/Templates/Content/General.aspx?NRMODE=Published&NRNODEGUID=%7b886D7D87-7306-4704-B8CF-7E88B1FF4DF4%7d&NRORIGINALURL=%2fAdministration%2fSupportPages%2fPrivacyStatement%2ehtm&NRCACHEHINT=NoModifyGuest#data)
  * We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below. 
  * If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose: by indicating in a box at the point on the site where personal data is collected 

## Disclosure and Visitor Choice 

  * We do not disclose, sell or rent in any way your personal data to our subsidiaries or any other organisations. 

## Confidentiality / Security 

  * We give visitors to our Web site the option of using a secure transmission method to send us their personal data. 
  * We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from: unauthorised access   
improper use or disclosure  
unauthorised modification   
unlawful destruction or accidental loss 
  * All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. 
  * We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to authorities except if required by law or other regulation. 

## Access to the personal data we may hold about you

  * You can ask us whether we are keeping personal data about you, by:   
sending an email: [info@WellingtonNZ.com](mailto:info@WellingtonNZ.com)   
sending postal mail to this address:  
Positively Wellington Tourism,   
PO Box 10 017  
Wellington 6011  
New Zealand  
calling this telephone number: +64 4 916 1205  

  * Upon request, which you can indicate by:   
sending an email: [info@WellingtonNZ.com](mailto:info@WellingtonNZ.com)   
sending postal mail to this address:  
Positively Wellington Tourism   
PO Box 10 017   
Wellington 6011   
New Zealand 
  * We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a week. - although we may before require proof of your identity -. We will provide the information without any charge. 
  * We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data:  
erased   
rectified or amended   
completed 
  * We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal. 
  * We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data. 

## Privacy Compliance 

  * Our privacy policy is compliant with the following instrument: Privcay Act 1993 

## Table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used 

Primary personal data/Business information   
x volunteered by each visitor   
\- collected from public records or bodies   
\- collected from private organisations 

| Primary personal data | Technical administration of the Web site  | Research & Development | Customer Administration  | Marketing | Trading in personal data Name   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Gender | 

-

| 

x

| 

-

| 

x

| 

-  
  
Address | 

-

| 

-

| 

-

| 

x

| 

-  
  
E-mail address  | 

-

| 

x

| 

-

| 

x

| 

-  
  
Phone/Fax number  | 

-

| 

-

| 

-

| 

x

| 

-  
  
other  | 

-

| 

x

| 

-

| 

x

| 

-  
  
Business Information | Technical administration of the Web site  | Research & Development | Customer Administration  | Marketing | Trading in personal data Name   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Gender | 

-

| 

-

| 

-

| 

-

| 

-  
  
Address | 

x

| 

x

| 

-

| 

-

| 

-  
  
E-mail address  | 

x

| 

x

| 

-

| 

-

| 

-  
  
Phone/Fax number  | 

x

| 

x

| 

-

| 

-

| 

-  
  
other  | 

x

| 

-

| 

-

| 

-

| 

-
